Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for!
One piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place!
That the end of the map reveals?
Is only legendary.
Till someone proves it real.
Through it all!
Through all the trouble of times!
Through the heartache!
And through the pain!
Know that I will be there!
To stand by you!
Like I know you'll stand by me!
So come aboard!
And bring along all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for!
There's always room for you!
If you want to be my friend!
We are, we are on the crew!
We are!
Okay, so tell us all about it?
I gotta admit, I'm curious.
I'll pass. Hey, wait!
I don't care about our past.
Where are you going, Luffy? For a walk.
A walk?
Do you mean you're not
gonna listen to this?
Nope.
Who's he?
Don't mind him.
That's just how he is.
We'll hear you out.
Though I can tell you right now, I
don't think it's gonna change anything.
Well, I'll listen, too.
It might help me make some sense out of
everything that's going on around here.
Me too.
I want to know all about her.
Now he's asleep. Hey!
You said you'd hear her out!
Hmm, I see.
This is why it was hard for her.
I fell asleep.
Oh no, Nojiko.
I wonder where she ran off to.
Just a little more, Bellomere.
Just a little more and
everything will be ours again.
Cocoyashi village, the
tangerine farm, everything.
It's taken eight years.
It's done!
Yay!
Now if I could just get that book.
Hey, is that you, Nami?
Do you need any help there?
No, I'm just looking.
I'll be going now.
That's too bad.
Damn it, Nami!
Not again, Sticky Fingers.
You little urchin.
How many times do I have to
tell you that stealing is wrong?
How else am I gonna get what I need?
I don't have any money.
Chipscake!
Bellamy! Bellamy!
I caught her stealing again!
Now open up this door!
What do you want now?
You're back.
That was a quick trip.
I got a ride.
Listen, you better get control of her
before she winds up in a jail cell.
Thanks for the advice.
Haven't you ever seen something
you've wanted and just taken it?
You're the reason she acts this way!
Relax, I'm just kidding.
I hope you were kind
enough to pay for her.
Uh, Bellamere?
Thanks so much.
I don't have the money right now.
I'll pay it somehow.
Does that sound good?
You can't say things like that!
Look, he's as red as a beet!
Now then, laugh it up
while you still can, Nami.
I'm sorry.
It's just that I really
need that book, Bellamere.
Then why didn't you ask me
if I would buy it for you?
Because I know you can't afford it.
Of course I can.
There's money left over
from the last harvest.
But I heard them in the village.
They said the weather's
been so good lately?
That everyone's tangerines will sell,
Which means we can't raise our price!
or we may not be able to sell at all.
They don't know what
they're talking about.
Way to go, Nami.
If I had stolen it, there's no
way I would have been caught.
No more stealing, right?
I was just joking, that's all.
That really hurt.
I'm sorry, but one thing's for sure.
The maps you draw are so amazing, Nami!
I see you can draw land maps
now as well as sea charts.
That's the map of our island, isn't it?
Nobody will believe that such a
little girl drew this all by herself.
I wanted the book so I'd be able
to start studying navigation.
Navigation as well?
You're going to be a
navigator? That's right.
I'm going to guide ships around
all the oceans of the world.
It'll be great.
And I'll be able to make maps of
all the far-off places I'll go.
So, this island map is a first
step toward realizing your dream.
Is that it?
Mm-hmm.
A world map, huh?
Nami, your dream is going to come true.
I have no doubt.
Hey, Othellamere. Hmm?
Why haven't you been eating
dinner with us lately?
I've been eating tangerines.
I've just been on a diet, that's all.
Then I don't want to eat either.
What's with all of the drama?
You need to eat because
you are a growing girl.
Why do you keep lying to us?
You're not eating because we don't
have enough money to buy food.
That's why. Really?
You're starving yourself
so that we won't go hungry.
Tangerines replenish my skin with
the power of liquid sunlight.
And they are the only reason I
am still such a ravishing beauty,
even though I am in my extreme late 20s.
But your hands are all yellow.
Would you just shut up
and eat your food already?
And here you go, Nami.
All done.
A Bellamere one-of-a-kind
original. Oh, great.
A hand-me-down.
Yeah, that's true.
But it suits you. See, look.
But the lion used to be a sunflower.
Quit complaining.
You have to take my hand-me-downs
or you won't get any new clothes.
But it's not fair.
You get new clothes all the
time and mine are all used.
I get old clothes too, you know.
So just suck it up, Nami,
and take what you get.
Understand?
We didn't come from the
same parents anyway.
We're not real sisters, so who cares?
Nami!
Bellamere, please!
So what if you don't
have the same parents?
I don't ever want to hear you
say anything like that again!
I don't care.
You're not even our real mother!
You're just some lady
who's taking care of us.
You wish we'd never come here so you
could buy clothes and food for yourself.
You'd be better off
without us, wouldn't you?
That way you could be selfish
and do whatever you want.
I wish...
I wish that one rich would have adopted
us instead of a sneaky loser like you!
Well, fine.
If you hate it here so much, you can go
find someplace else to live if you want.
I didn't sign up for this.
Stop fighting!
Please, just stop!
I'm never coming back!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Valamere, the three of us are a family.
That's the truth!
And you know Nami feels the
same, no matter what she said.
Look who's being the adult here.
I blew up, and you're
the level-headed one.
Why don't you go and find Nami?
I'll make something special for
dinner, and we can all make up, okay?
Sorry, lady.
Two for five is the
lowest price I can offer.
Isn't that really your best offer?
Half off.
Today only.
Fresh produce.
You won't find a lower
price anywhere today.
I guarantee it or you're money back.
So you've run away from home
and come to the village.
Now what's the plan?
Drink before it gets cold.
Bellamere would be so much happier if
she didn't have to take care of us?
And why would you say that?
Well, you need a lot of money
to take care of two kids.
And because of me, the whole
village hates her right now.
That's progress.
At least you're considering others.
But don't worry.
When Bellamere was your age,
he was a complete nightmare.
terrorizing the entire village.
Is that the truth? Sure.
Even now the villagers look at
her as some kind of a Scrap.
So you can imagine how surprised everyone
in the village was when she joined up?
with the marines, huh?
Marines?
You mean Bellamere was in
the marines? That's right.
She said she couldn't stand by and do
nothing while pirates killed innocent people.
Then she left the village.
She was teetering on the
verge of death when...
If this is the end, then so be it.
Your little sister?
Uh-uh.
I found her.
How did she survive?
That innocent child was you, Nami.
And seeing how precious you were gave
Bellamy the right reasons to live again.
It is a ship! I knew it!
Who on earth would be out
in such a terrible storm?
Doctor.
I need a doctor.
What's going on?
What happened to you, Bellamere?
Bellamere!
Did somebody call for a doctor?
Who are these children? Doctor!
They're burning up.
I'm afraid they might be really sick.
Please, help them.
Give them here.
All right, and we'd better mend up those
nasty wounds of yours as well, young lady.
Never mind me!
Please, just don't let them die.
You have to save me.
Him I'm begging
you doctor I don't
believe it say that whole thing again
I said I'm gonna try To be the mother
of these two girls it's that simple
no way that's insane you are far
too Immature to handle this much
responsibility you can't handle them by
yourself just hand them over to the...
I've made my mind!
You can't deny that I'm an adult,
and what I've lived through
as a Marine has given
me the right to be
treated with more respect.
I'm perfectly capable of
taking care of these two girls.
And nothing can stop me from
raising them to be wonderful.
girls.
So now we're going to
be a family together.
Nami and Nochiko have
renewed my love of life.
The bond between the three of you girls
goes far deeper than any normal family.
Mommy, I thought I'd
find you here. Nojiko?
Come on, Bellomere's waiting for us.
She's making us a special supper.
Sure.
I think she's making your favorite.
Omelettes are good to eat, son!
I love omelettes! Alright!
The pirates are coming!
Everybody run!
Hide!
The Arlong Pirates! Arlong?
That's impossible!
Why would Fishman from
the Grand Line come here?
The rumor about the split between
the Fishman and Pirates must be true!
Nami! Nojiko! Genzo!
It's too dangerous for you here.
Go hide in the woods.
What about... You must go! Now!
Greetings and salutations,
you pathetic little humans.
From this moment on, this entire island and
its inhabitants are a part of my domain.
Listen closely.
From now on, on the first day of every
month, you will buy your lives from me.
100,000 berries for adults,
50,000 for children.
Those who cannot pay will die.
What should we do, Nojiko?
We don't have that much money.
Maybe the fishmen won't
be able to find our house.
You can't see it from here.
Is that it?
So what's the haul?
About 25 million, give or take.
You all shall live.
It looks like we each have
to pay 100,000 berries
to these fishmen every
month just to stay alive No,
there's no way we could survive We
don't have a choice We should just be
happy that nobody in the village has been
killed yet If all they want is money,
that's an easy price to pay
I just hope they leave without noticing
Bellamere's house With two children,
she'd need 200,000 berries
There's no way she has that much saved.
It's time to leave.
Come, brothers.
Arlong, there's smoke coming
from outside the village.
Okay.
Let's see.
Delicious.
There isn't anything quite as tasty
as my special tangerine sauce.
Nami and Nojiko are gonna love it.
It looks like chimney smoke
from somebody's house.
Oh, we almost missed that one.
Bellomir!
All right, let's go, guys.
This is bad.
The pirates are going to Bellomir's house!
Genzo, look!
Nojiko and Nami are gone!
What did you say?
I think the duck needs another ten
minutes and the stew is almost ready.
This is definitely
going to blow my budget,
but sometimes you've got to live a little.
Bellamere!
Bellamere's going to be killed!
We will not abandon Villamir!
Damn it!
Why did this happen?
Hold on, Villamir!
Oh, they're here.
It's open!
Come in!
Why, thanks!
I guess you weren't
expecting a former marine.
Now what would a pirate from the Grand
Line want with Cocoyashi Village?
What's so funny?
Useless, foolish,
stupid, empty, worthless.
All of you humans, you have
no strength to speak on.
We'll help her escape
through the back door!
What if the pirates are already there?
It'll be okay! Stop!
Doctor!
You can't go back home! What?
But we have to save Bellamere!
No, Gecko, Nami, quiet and listen to me.
There will be times.
Times in life like this moment now.
When you have to learn the truth,
no matter how hard it is to take.
It's no use.
These guys are real monsters,
and I'm going to die.
No, Chico.
No, me.
Bellamy, don't waste your life
because you're a stubborn fool.
There's no reason for
this fight when it can
be resolved with a
simple exchange of money.
Just pay the fee, and I'll stop.
$100,000 for each adult and
$50,000 for each kid, if any.
If you can pay for your whole family,
I'd gladly spare your lives. Family?
How much money do you have?
You need $200,000.
I don't have it.
I'm not even close.
Hey, the table is set for three in here?
A family of three.
It's for me and my friend.
We were supposed to have
a nice dinner tonight.
Before you came.
Come, Bellamere!
I know you've made something wonderful.
Pay them before our food gets cold.
Just pay the pirates.
And then they'll leave us alone.
Now everyone is saved!
It's true!
The village register shows no record
of her marrying or giving birth.
She's always been single.
Listen!
There's no way that the pirates
will ever find out about you.
But you have to leave
this island immediately!
And don't ever look back!
It's the only way for all
three of you to survive!
We can't afford it any other way!
You're much too young to be at sea alone!
But you've survived before!
And if there's even a chance! No!
I don't want to!
I want to stay in this village!
It's because!
We're poor!
That's why we can't stay together.
Why?
Why can't they just go away?
Well then.
Now we can all be safe.
Fine, we'll leave this island.
We have to leave or Pelomir will die.
Wait, who said I was paying for me?
That money I gave up was
for my two daughters.
But I can't pay you!
What are you doing? It's okay.
I have to do this for my family!
Even if it costs me my life!
Stupid girl.
It's true the three of us
aren't related by blood.
But we're family.
All I've ever wanted
was to be their mother.
And now, I can be.
What? No!
I wish that one rich would have adopted us
instead of a stinky loser
like you It was a lie!
I was lying, Bellamy!
Don't cry, girls.
I wish I could have...
I could have provided for you better.
I wish I could have been a
better mother to the both of you.
Don't say that!
We don't need anything!
Just don't die!
Don't leave us!
You need to see the map!
I'm going to drive the whole world!
Yes, your map.
Go and make your dreams come true.
For me.
Tha, I'm here now!
So these are your daughters?
Yeah, that's right.
And you have promised me
that you'll leave them alone.
No problem, as long as you
die like a good girl. Papa!
AAAAAAAH!
Well then, don't kill him, boys.
No, just teach him a lesson.
Now to set an example.
You ready to die?
Nojiko! Nami!
Love you.